LAMAN GULIYEVA

00994553163264 • leman.guliyeva@outlook.com • https://www.linkedin.com/in/laman-guliyeva/

Summary

I am a psychologist with 3 years of experience in administrative and organizational work. I am a reliable and hardworking person with excellent communication skills and I have proven ability to manage projects successfully. I strengthened my skills and knowledge in the field of Human Resources and I am dedicated to developing further.

Professional Experience

Training and Development Junior Specialist

Sinteks Group of Companies, Baku, Azerbaijan

February 2022-Present

- Organize and deliver Sales technique and Customer Service trainings
- Arrange evaluation sessions for sales personnel and report results accordingly
- Support organization process of training sessions for Sales Development program
- Organize an adaptation program
- · Fill in all feedback and results into Training Database and maintain with updated data
- Assists in organizing relevant trainings for company employees on request
- Supports the implementation of all processes related to the activities of the T&D

Trainer November 2021 – March 2022

Erasmus Student Network (ESN) Azerbaijan, Baku, Azerbaijan

- Preparing training program on "Career Building" for the "Digiuth.com" online learning platform
- Deliver online courses in Azerbaijani and English
- Research and development of self-assessment tools and effective training strategy

Human Resources Intern

September 2021 – November 2021

ABB Bank, Baku, Azerbaijan

- Closely involved in the application of HR functions and came up with new ideas
- Prepared presentations for the management
- Found and contacted vendor companies that train employees,
- Assisted organizers at important events and training for employees
- Analyzed data and statistics
- Execution of HR documentation, planning and evaluation of recruitment needs

Front Office Coordinator / Call Lead Operator

March 2020 - September 2021

Code Academy, Baku, Azerbaijan

- Delivered administrative support to office staff, promoting excellence in office operations
- Schedule/confirm appointments with clients, take record of the new lead, register client to the CRM
- Communicate with clients on social media, receive and make calls, inform about products
- Assisting student to prepare CV, applying for jobs positions, giving feedbacks and career consultations
- Organizing the final project presentations of the groups, sending invitations, giving feedbacks
- Finding group mentors, organizing interviews and making contracts
- Announcing job vacancies, processing recruitment and resignation processes

Human Resources Intern

September 2019 - November 2019

GDG Professionals (HR Management & Consulting), Baku, Azerbaijan

- Preparing training materials and presentations
- Recruiting and hiring: reviewing resumes and conducting interviews
- Organize and schedule meetings and appointments, communicating with external partners
- Supply office with necessary equipment and tools
- Updating CV databases internally and management of the web pages

• Taking part in different HRM projects

Administrative Assistant

Khazar University, Baku, Azerbaijan

March 2016 - January 2017

- Organization of conferences and annual career fairs
- Research of company lists and conference speakers
- Editing web pages of Career Development Center
- Preparation of registration templates, training materials for the workshops and trainings
- Translation of announcements
- Distribution of vacancies' announcement among students and alumni

Education

KHAZAR UNIVERSITY, Baku, Azerbaijan

2015 - 2019

26/04/2016 - 18/05/2016

Bachelor of Science in Humanities, Education and Social Sciences

(concentration: <u>Psychology</u>)

Honors Diploma. GPA: 90/100 or (3.66/4.0).

- Dean's Honor List I and II Semester of 2017-2018 Academic Year
- Dean's Honor List I Semester of 2018-2019 Academic Year

Language Skills Soft Skills

Azerbaijani - (Native)

English - Advanced (IELTS 7.5)

Turkish - Advanced Spanish - Elementary 1. Critical thinking 2. Professional Responsibility

3. Adaptability 4. Openness to learn 5. Public speaking

Hard Skills

Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, Access, Power Point, Outlook. / Social Media Management / Web Browsing & Web Based Application

Training & Conferences

→ Linkedin Learning: Strategic Human Resources, by Catherine Mattice Zundel	10/01/2022 - 11/01/2022
→ Trauma Psychotherapy - Intervention skills by Bahattin Göktan (training & supervision).	14/12/2021 - 07/01/2022
→ Coursera: Positive Psychology, I. Martin Seligmans' Visionary Science;	
II. Applications and Interventions - authorized by University of Pennsylvania.	08/2019 - 09/2019
→ Nizami Ganjavi International Center: VII Global Baku Forum (Certificate of Appreciation).	10/03/2019 - 17/03/2019
→ European Confederation of Psychoanalytic Psychotherapies (ECPP): Transcultural Aspects	
of Psychoanalysis: "Theory and Method", (Certificate of Participation).	14/06/2018 - 15/06/2018
→ Khazar University: IV International Psychology Conference (Certificate of Appreciation).	07/04/2018 - 08/04/2018
→ EdVenture Partners & Facebook: Fall 2017 Peer to Peer: Facebook Global Digital Challenge.	
project: "The Chain", (Certificate of Participation).	06/10/2017 - 06/12/2017
→ European Federation of Psychology Students' Associations (EFPSA): "Discover The Cultural	
Spirit" Turkey-Azerbaijan Psychology Student Exchange Program, Istanbul.	22/10/2017 - 29/10/2017
→ AIESEC & Human Foundation: "Development and Empowerment Program for Teen Girls	
and Young Women, (Certificate of Participation)	25/07/2017 - 30/08/2017
→ European Federation of Psychology Students' Associations: 31st EFPSA Congress.	23/04/2017 - 30/04/2017
"Humanity today - Individuals & Society", Gakh (Certificate of Participation)	

→ Khazar Un. Career Development Center: "Effective Communication Skills" Training.

